{
    "id": "adff4451dd55455eafd630a024480194",
    "title": "Good And Well Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "That was a …………………… film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3b7785ecc534d919669fc8d7de22064"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks Chinese …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a412e4adb25474ebf743220f692ef79"
        },
        {
            "question": "The steak smells …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d529909c85bf496aa57b09cd05e8ee42"
        },
        {
            "question": "My new car runs …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "71201ee79d8c42d2813c9c650f69e708"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sings really ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "78c8449140a34abfbbea67c4c74d0d00"
        },
        {
            "question": "I admire her. She is a ………………… writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "684f6e71d1a74653a5627ef5c4255970"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her English is very …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5f8a5d3d53d4c3988806ab0ffc06119"
        },
        {
            "question": "The holiday did me a lot of …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7313707db0b4c6789096879a8bfc484"
        },
        {
            "question": "They gave me some ………………….. advice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9f285d959e024ad5bd59e7748b3ea428"
        },
        {
            "question": "We think …………………… of him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a3b1a4114a645e4aae2df623fac25a7"
        }
    ]
}